《神盾局特工》前情回顾
Previously on "Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."...
我发了誓  我们都发了誓
I swore an oath. We all did.
保护世界受到更疯狂世界的侵害
To protect the world against the much weirder world.
这一定是发送给神盾局内部的
It's got to be some sort of activation signal
九头蛇成员的激活信号
to Hydra members within S.H.I.E.L.D.
我们之中一直有内奸
We've had a wolf in the herd the whole time.
沃德是九头蛇
他们渗入了我们组织的最高层
They've infiltrated the highest levels of our organization.
-沃德  -别这样  沃德  你没必要这样做
- Ward! Ward! - Ward, you don't have to do this!
菲兹  他没事吧
Fitz -- is he okay?
他还活着
He's alive.
我代表美国武装部队
On behalf of the united states armed forces,
命令你们投降
I order you to stand down.
我们不是九头蛇
We're not Hydra.
我们是神盾局特工
We're agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.
现在  在其他人眼里
Well, right now, to the rest of the world,
那是一码事
that's the same thing.
弗瑞总是说当人明白自己在参与
Fury always said a man can accomplish anything
一项伟大的事业  便能无往不利
when he realizes he's a part of something bigger.
你想让我重新开始  重建神盾局
You want me to start over, rebuild S.H.I.E.L.D.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
我称这里为操场  见到你真是荣幸  长官
I call it the playground. It is an honor to meet you, sir.
我知道我们没什么东西  但你尽可以利用
I know we don't have much, but what we have is yours,
科尔森局长
Director Coulson.
漫威公司出品
1945年  奥地利
我应该不用提醒你时间紧迫吧
I don't think I need to remind you that the clock is ticking.
马上装箱完毕
We are almost finished loading.
怀特霍尔先生  恐怕施密特...
Herr Whitehall, I-I fear Schmidt --
用不着害怕红骷髅了[《美国队长》]
Oh, there's no reason left to fear the Red Skull.
他死了
He's dead.
然而  他的意志没有死
However, his vision is not.
九头蛇的使命要继续下去
The work Hydra has done will live on.
-方尖碑呢  -他们正要拿出来
- The obelisk? - They are bringing it out now.
希望他们小心点
Carefully, I hope.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我以为这里只收藏遗物
I thought this stockpile held only artifacts.
从土里挖出来的
Not everything we dug out of the ground
不都是文物  朋友
was an antique, my friend.
有一些很先进的物件
Some of it was quite advanced.
那些人死掉是因为这个吗
Is this the reason these men...?
翻译：草草扑倒海莉  大卫熊   milkon
■
是的
Hmm? Ja.
红骷髅说这东西可能
The Red Skull said it may hold the answer --
翻译：silence  欧沈娜  小欠  小茗
解释关于死亡的一切
the answer to death itself.
翻译：苏小黛  王大可  木浅熏
时间轴：灵媒  凭陵新月  信徒
他们还挺努力的  这我得承认
I'll give them an "A" for effort.
你们好啊  老实点
Guten tag, boys. All right, nice and calm.
校对：胖兔纯  还我菲兹熊
都别动  不然我们就把雷管绑在你们...
No sudden moves, or we'll tie a blasting cap to your...
后期：瓜瓜     总监：米小勒
杜根  "蛋蛋"用德语怎么说
Hey, Dugan, what's the german word for "Nuts"?
不知道  吉姆
I don't know, Jim.
不过绑上之后  他们会说出这个词的
But tie a blasting cap to them, I'll bet we'll hear it.
放下
Put it down.
我说放下
Down.
现在这些物件都
These assets are now under the protection
由战略科学军团保管
of the Strategic Scientific Reserve.
他们会被转移  永远藏匿
They'll be relocated and hidden out of sight, indefinitely...
你也是
as will you.
砍掉一颗头  会再长出两个
Cut off one head, two more shall grow in its place.
那就一直砍呗
Then I guess we'll keep cutting them off.
带他出去
Get him out of here.
好了  伙计们  装箱吧
All right, boys, let's pack it up.
卡特特工  这都是什么啊
Agent Carter, what the hell is all this stuff?
危险物件
Dangerous.
现在我们得装载所有物件
Right now, we need to contain everything
撤离敌区
and get it out of enemy territory.
史塔克先生今晚要过目这些
Mr. Stark plans to go through it tonight.
至于这个  谁都别碰
And that, we must never touch.
这是我们已知最后的九头蛇据点了
This is the last Hydra site we know of.
终于打败他们了
They're finally beaten.
可你并不开心
You don't sound thrilled.
这些东西不能装箱就完事了
Well, these things can't simply be boxed up.
和平期间应该建立一个专门的部门
Someone needs to establish a permanent unit during peacetime.
防止危险科技落入恶人手中
To keep dangerous technology contained?
同时防止史塔克这样的人拿这些东西"玩耍"
And watch over people like Stark who are toying with it.
在那之前  我们能做的
Until then, all we can do
装箱  紧锁  尽我们的努力
is box it up, lock it up, and dedicate ourselves
保证这些东西不见天日
to making sure it never sees the light of day.
现世  维吉尼亚州亚历山大市
我们收到声讯了  他们谈判已开始
We've got ears on them. The package is in the open.
交易完成前别动手
Don't engage until the deal's done.
明白
Copy that.
崔普  有视频了吗
Trip, we got eyes?
有了
Now we do.
这是我卖的东西
That's what I'm selling.
我知道你们想看证件
I'm sure you'd like to see some credentials.
布朗宁特工  作为前神盾局的人
Agent Browning, for ex-S.H.I.E.L.D.,
你似乎毫不在意我们是谁
you seem awfully indifferent to who we are.
你们是出价最高的人
What you are is the highest bidder.
你们是为了钱还是为了九头蛇
Whether you're in it for profit or for Hydra,
现在都与我无关了
it doesn't concern me, not anymore.
我们就想听到这句
That's what we want to hear.
他们要买的是什么
What are they buying from him?
是情报  不是东西
Intel, not hardware.
我想知道的是
The mystery I'd like to solve is,
我们凭什么要付你这么多钱
why should we be paying you so much?
这看上去就是个箱子  抱歉  箱子的照片
This looks like a box. Sorry -- a picture of a box...
而且这照片上的箱子还不在你手上
A picture of a box you don't have.
箱子在政府那儿
The government has it,
连同其他数千件他们从神盾局没收的物品
along with thousands of other assets they've seized from s.H.I.E.L.D.,
而且其中半数他们都无法理解
and they don't know what to make of half of them.
我在一间神盾局防范设施工作
I worked in a S.H.I.E.L.D. containment facility
里面有几百个跟这一样的箱子
that had hundreds of boxes that look just like this.
但只有这一个箱子
But this is the only one
有十级权限的文件
that has a level 10 classified file dedicated to it.
你卖的不过是海底针
You're selling us a needle in a haystack.
找到大海得靠你们
Finding the haystack is up to you.
我听过你们的大名  你们一定做得到
I know your reputation. I'm sure you'll be fine.
但我不喜欢你们说好了条件现在又反悔
What I don't appreciate is you changing the terms on me now.
我们只是想要个解释  布朗宁
We're asking for clarification, Browning.
是你违反了协议
You're the one who changed the terms,
带了不止我们说好的两名护卫
bringing more than the two guards we agreed upon.
我只带了两名护卫来
I only brought two guards.
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
你们怎么在这儿
What the hell are you doing here?
那是谁
Who was that?
第三方[派对]
A third party.
你管那叫派对
A party's what you'd call that?
他没影了
He's gone.
这里可是25英尺高
25-foot drop.
这本是卧底行动
This was supposed to be an undercover operation.
你们为什么跟着我们
You want to explain why you're shadowing us?
我们是你们的后援  你们正需要
We were your backup, which you needed.
是啊  他也需要
Yeah. So did he.
长官  目标死了
Sir, mark's down.
第三方干的  可能是九头蛇  我们暴露了
Third party, possibly Hydra, and we're out in the open.
什么命令
What are our orders?
隐匿
Go dark.
神盾局特工
第二季 第一集
操场  地点:保密
他们是逃犯  他们应该受到惩罚
They're fugitives, and they deserve to be punished.
我们目睹了历史上最大的一次
We witnessed the single greatest intelligence collapse
情报机构垮台  乔治
in recorded history, George.
我们有义务为美国人民抓到责任人
We have a duty to the American people to hunt down those responsible.
所以我经常通宵不眠
So, no, I don't sleep most nights.
塔伯特准将  您说您将神盾局人员和
General Talbot, you said you have s.H.I.E.L.D. personnel
武器都锁在了监禁设施内
and weaponry locked in a secure facility,
那么是否能说神盾局
so is it fair to say that S.H.I.E.L.D.
以及渗透进其中的九头蛇恐怖分子
and the Hydra terrorists who poisoned its ranks
已被击败
have been defeated?
这个腐败的机构已被瓦解
The corrupt institution has been dismantled, yes.
我们砍下了大树
We cut down the tree,
还拔起了树根  但这么说吧
we pulled up the roots, but let's just say
等我们把他们都扔进篝火烧光我才会安心
I'll rest easier when we throw it all on the bonfire.
那么还没都抓住吗
So, you didn't get them all?
多亏我们的黑市线人
Our black-market contacts
那人才相信我们不是神盾局的
were the reason the guy believed we weren't with s.H.I.E.L.D.
科尔森认识哈特利
Coulson knows Hartley.
她是你们之中他唯一信任的人
She's the only person on your team he trusts.
但你们为什么现身
But why'd you break silhouette protocol?
-他下了命令  -命令
- He ordered us to. - Orders.
有特工跟踪  我们无法维护卧底身份
We can't maintain solid cover with agents tailing us.
我们还不敢肯定你不会拿钱跑路呢
And we can't be sure you won't run off with the money.
你知道那个怪物怎么找到我们的吗  哈特利
Any idea how that freak show found us, Hartley?
我有个理论
I have a theory.
够了  他说我们是出价最高者
Cool it. The man said we were the highest bidder.
那么说他一定广撒网来着
That means he sent the word out wide.
然后自食其果了
And he paid for that mistake.
-是啊  -这么说太轻了
- Yes, he did. - That's an understatement.
梅特工
Agent May.
斯凯特工
Agent Skye.
兰斯·亨特
Lance Hunter.
哈特利特工
Agent Hartley.
行动不顺利吗
Operation didn't go well, I take it?
-怎么看出来的  -真可惜
- What gave you that idea? - That's a shame, man.
我还希望你们去找的那个特工
I was hoping that agent you were scoping out
手里有我们用得上的设备呢
would have some tech we could use.
抱歉了  迈克  没有新玩具
Sorry, Mack. No new toys.
找到任何东西了吗
You get anything?
新敌人
A new enemy.
我知道
I know. I know.
局长要你们去做报告
Director wants you for debrief.
我也想说说呢  把他放在大屏幕上吧
The feeling is mutual. Throw him up on the big screen.
我们告诉敌人现在刀枪不入了
We'll tell him that his enemies have gone bulletproof.
他在办公室
He's in his office.
科尔森在这儿  这么大的事不早说  比尔
Coulson's here? Kind of buried the lead there, Bill.
他只见梅特工
Just Agent May.
收到
Copy that.
不是吧
Really?
告诉他我也想发表意见
Well, tell him I'd like to voice my opinion, too,
居然什么都不告诉我
On being kept in the dark,
我不喜欢被排除...在外
'cause I don't like being left...out.
赶紧习惯吧
Get used to it.
话说  子弹打不动那家伙
So, the guy was bulletproof, huh?
太酷了
That's sweet.
怎么弄的  穿了防弹服之类的吗
What... like, protective clothing or...?
也许吧  我们发现了这些金属碎片
Maybe. We found these metal shards.
子弹击中他时弹落的
They broke off with the bullet hits.
我拿去实验室看看
I'm gonna take it to the lab.
我会告诉科尔森
I'll let Coulson know.
真高兴见到他
It'll be good to see him...
如果他肯让我见的话
If I see him.
他可是个大忙人
He's a busy man.
抱歉  我只能告诉你这么多了
Sorry. That's all I can give you.
尽量小心点
Try to move up with your head down.
还有  以后只能用秘密情报点联系
And, hey, only use the dead drop from now on.
现在国内没剩多少公用电话了
There aren't enough pay phones left in this country.
来了啊
Hi.
你是负责人  但我是负责你的  记得吗
You're the man in charge, but I'm in charge of you, remember?
我有两条规矩
I had two rules.
避免出外勤
Avoid field operations...
还有每隔几天就要向我报到
And check in with me every few days.
上次到现在已经两周了
It's been two weeks.
我今晚还要搭飞机走
And I'm flying back out tonight.
我得集中精力招募新人
I have to focus on recruitment.
都快让我精疲力尽了
It's starting to wear me down.
时间问题吗
The hours?
是人数问题
The numbers.
在各种卖国贼  军事在押犯
Between the traitors, military detainees,
还有出卖商业机密的人中
And the sell-outs in the private sector,
那些有可能会忠于神盾局的人
The people who could possibly be considered loyal to S.H.I.E.L.D.
实在不好发现
is not impressive.
而且他们散落在全球各地
And they're scattered all over the damn globe.
没办法  你只能去面对面跟他们交谈
Well, you have no choice but to meet them face-to-face,
-好了解他们  -我知道  我也愿意
- Get a read on them. - I know, and I prefer it.
可坐经济舱飞来飞去太苦逼了
But flying economy blows.
隐身设备有进展了吗
Any progress on the cloaking equipment?
说得好像我知道似的
Like I can tell.
我们现在急需这东西
Well, we need it now, badly.
我们的飞机已经在地上趴了好几个月了
Our plane's been gathering dust for months,
可我还是不能冒险去开
But I still can't risk a takeoff
这货正想把我们推进火坑呢
with this guy trying to throw us on a bonfire,
看来还是只能去坐经济舱了
So flying coach it is...
飞机紧急出口边的位子通常空间较大
不过我从伦敦回来时坐到了紧急出口边的位子
Though I did score an exit row on the way back from london.
-你去伦敦干什么  -如有必要...
- And what was in london? - Allies...
盟友们已经准备好了
ready to be activated, if necessary.
这是个良好的开始
It's a decent start,
但如果没有更多资源  进程就会很缓慢
But it's gonna be slow-going without more resources.
这方面的消息可不好
Bad news on that front.
我们本来希望布朗宁特工会是朋友
We were hoping Agent Browning would be a friend.
即便不是  至少能卖技术给我们
And if not, at least sell us tech.
结果两样都落空了
Negative on both.
这刺客...九头蛇吗
The assassin...Hydra?
很有可能  甚至可能有异能
Likely. Possibly gifted.
他杀了布朗宁  他冲着情报去的
Killed browning. He wanted the intel.
估计又是一个084
Another 0-8-4, I guess.
你怎么评价哈特利的人
What's your assessment of Hartley's people?
你知道我怎么想的
You know what I think.
他们是雇佣兵  只为钱办事
They're mercenaries, here for the money.
你的客观评价是什么
But what's your assessment?
他们是优秀的雇佣兵
They're good mercenaries.
哈利特做过很多年卧底
Well, Hartley spent a lot of years undercover.
结交的朋友自然是那种人  如果她信任他们
Those are the kinds of friends you make. If she trusts them...
怎么了
What?
战略科学军团  我刚知道这个
S.S.R. I just read about this.
这在史书里是找不到的
It's not in any of the history books.
不  它在弗瑞的工具箱里
No. It's in Fury's toolbox.
凯尼格  取消我的航班
Koenig, cancel my flights.
这能说明什么
What did it say about this?
084可能是任何东西  这我们是知道的
An 0-8-4 could be anything... that much we've learned.
这不只是某个084  这是第一个
It's not just an 0-8-4. It's the first.
弗瑞只知道  跟这东西沾边  没少死人
And all Fury knew about was the trail of bodies that follows it.
塔伯特说他把双方都击败了
Talbot's saying he's beaten both sides,
而我们只是在地下躲藏
but we're just hiding underground.
如果九头蛇拿到这个
If hydra gets their hands on this,
那他们可能就不用躲了
They may not have to.
九头蛇万岁
Hail hydra.
嗯
Yeah.
东西安全吗
Is the package secure?
正在上传
Uploading now.
他期待一个正面的结果
He expected a positive result
并寄出了一份礼物作为奖赏
and sent a gift along as a reward...
为这次和下次的任务
for this assignment and the next.
一枚钻石
A diamond.
铍铝镁锌石  开采自马达加斯加岛的洞穴里
Musgravite, from the caves of Madagascar,
世界上最罕见的宝石之一
one of the rarest gemstones in the world.
他认为你会很喜欢它的结构
He believes you'll find its structure quite pleasurable.
他说的对吗
Was he right?
他总是对的
He's always right.
但总比你在布达佩斯做的东西强
Whatever. It's better than that crap you cooked up in Budapest.
我的选择很少  是就地取材
I didn't have much to work with. It was farm to table.
-那弄伤了我的牙  -因为你是英国人
- It broke my tooth. - That's 'cause you're English.
-哈特利  亨特  爱达荷  -什么事
- Hartley, Hunter, Idaho. - What's the word?
去他办公室
In his office.
局长要求观众到场了吗
The director requests an audience?
这人不提要求
Oh, the man doesn't do requests.
听着  我们进去以后  不论做什么
And, listen, when we get in there, no matter what you do,
别看他的眼睛
don't look him in the eye.
真的吗
Really?
不是  骗你的
Nah, he's all right.
但你们都要注意一下
But you should both focus on
不要说太傻的事
not saying anything overly stupid.
-遵命  女士  -我可不保证
- Yes, ma'am. - I'm not making any promises.
你把那个材料送去实验室了吗
You took the material to the lab?
那是现在最要紧的事
That's the top priority now.
是的  但我不知道结果会怎样
Yeah. But I don't know what it'll get us.
他今天心情怎么样
How's the mood in there today?
他已经尽力了
It's as good as can be expected.
菲兹  现在我希望你能够测试
Fitz, now would be the time I'd have you test
金属的共振频率
the resonant frequencies of the metal
那样我就能鉴别出这是什么物质了
so that I could determine what properties we're dealing with.
菲兹
Fitz?
菲兹  能听到我说话吗
Fitz? Can you even hear me?
是的  西蒙斯  我听到了
Yes, Simmons, I can hear you.
我正在听你要求的
I'm trying to hear the bloody resonant frequency
这该死的共振频率  但我只能听到你说话
you keep going on about, but all I can hear is you.
冷静点  我只是问问
Calm down. I'm only asking.
你还没有分离出
You haven't been able to isolate --
没有  我还没分离出
No, I haven't been able to isolate the...
那个
the, um...
the...
-振荡频率  -是的
- rate of oscillation. - Yes.
其实我正要说呢
I was just about to say that, actually.
但我没说是因为
And, no, I haven't because it keeps...
那词叫什么来着  告诉我那个词
What's the word again? Give me the word.
-波动  -是的  对的
- Fluctuating. - Yes. Good. Fine.
谢谢  走开
Thanks. Go away.
你吃药了吗
Have you taken your medication?
吃了
Yes.
别  别
Don't. Don't.
别碰任何东西
Please don't touch anything.
这是飞机的隐形技术
That's the cloaking technology for the plane.
-怎么样了  -还不错
- How's it coming? - Good.
比我希望的要慢
Slower than I'd like.
我遇到些障碍  但是快完成了
I've had a few bumps, but it's -- I'm close.
我不需要你来插手
And I don't need you mucking it up.
菲兹  我只是想帮忙
Fitz, I'm trying to help.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
但我也知道隐形技术多么重要
But I also know how important cloaking is, okay?
所以我只希望大家都
So I just need everybody to be...
大家都
everybody to be...
我只需要大家都
I just need everybody to be, um...
-耐心点  -对的
- Patient. - Yes.
你需要对自己耐心点  菲兹
You need to be patient with yourself, Fitz.
你就快成功了
You're almost there.
是的
Yeah.
是的  我就快成功了
Yeah, I'm almost there.
我们找到的金属有什么新进展吗
Any update on the metal we found?
有  有的
Yeah. Yep. Yep.
没有  其实  没有
Um, no. Actually, no.
我现在遇到些困难无法
I'm just having a bit of trouble identifying the...
无法
a bit of trouble --
我现在遇到些困难无法辨别这种材料
I'm having a bit of trouble identifying the material.
好吧
Okay.
是的  这与我们子弹的铅是一样的
Yeah, so, this is the same lead that we use in our bullets,
但这其中
but there's...
有些
there is something...
血
bleeding. Uh...
好的  这  你看到了吗
Okay. That's -- are you -- can you see that?
-看起来像肉  -是的  看到了
- Looks like flesh. - Yeah, I see it.
-是血  -很好
- It's blood. - Good.
我是说  这好怪
I mean, that's -- what? That's weird.
你能鉴别出是谁的血吗
Can you figure out whose blood?
那应该不会太困难
That shouldn't be too hard.
我会留下帮忙
I'll stay and help anyway.
这个人有超能力
So the man had powers?
我们对那个家伙射空了弹夹
We emptied our mags at the guy.
跟飞吻一样没效果
Might as well have been blowing kisses.
我从没见过这样的事
Never seen anything like it.
我有
I have.
而且一般遇到这种情况
And usually these encounters
都会有更好的经济补偿
come with better financial compensation.
-亨特  -怎么啦
- Hunter... - What?
别这么随便
Don't be yourself right now.
你就喜欢我这样哎
You like me like this.
你俩都有你们各自的神盾局传统
Look, you both have your S.H.I.E.L.D. traditions
说着那些废话
and all that nonsense,
还有要谨慎对待此事的个人原因
and personal reasons for being dedicated to the cause,
但是你认识我很久了  伊兹
but you've known me a long time, Izzy.
你知道能让我起床的动力是什么
And what gets me out of bed in the morning?
他不是顾全大局的人
He's not a "Big picture" Kind of guy.
我前妻也这么说
Sound like my ex-wife.
那她的话你也该听
And you should have listened to her, too.
DNA找到匹配了
DNA match.
卡尔·克里尔  他也在名录里
Carl Creel. He was on the index.
更重要的是  还被划掉了
More importantly, crossed off the index.
神盾局规定
S.H.I.E.L.D. protocol.
有时  一些具敌意的超能者会被消灭
Sometimes hostile gifted individuals are put down.
看来他们这工作做的不好啊
Well, they didn't do a great job here.
他们就没做
They didn't try.
看看监管特工是谁
Check who was the supervising agent.
约翰·加勒特特工
Agent John Garrett.
他们肯定是谎称克里尔被除掉后雇佣了他
They must have faked Creel's termination, recruited him.
至少我们现在知道他是九头蛇的人了
Well, now we know he's Hydra.
约翰·加勒特
John Garrett?
那不是你那个朋友吗
Isn't that your mate who, you know...
就是走上邪途的那个
Went to the dark side?
没错  然后他就疯了
Oh, yeah. Then he went nuts.
有点奇怪
It's a little bit strange.
我是说  他们完全一样
I mean, they're exactly the same.
你觉得他们只是双胞胎那么简单吗
You really think they were just twins?
我才不信
Come on.
我已经听过你所有的理论了  崔普
I have heard all your theories, Trip.
而且凯尼格总是不停的说他的另一个兄弟
And Koenig's always mentioning other brothers.
一天一个新的
Every day, another brother.
要是他再提起一个
If he brings up one more brother,
我非疯了不可
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
科尔森说我们可以信任他
Coulson said we can trust him.
这里有蹊跷
There's something fishy going on there, man.
总盯着这玩意儿你非疯了不可
You'll go crazy staring at this crap.
再说一遍  这是什么来着
What is it again?
还不确定
Not sure.
加勒特在摆弄的什么东西
Something Garrett was messing with.
科尔森一个月前丢给我的
Coulson put me on it a month ago,
让我在网络上深入查询  甚是用涨潮的路子去找
searching deep web contacts, even Rising Tide,
看看有没有匹配
looking for a match.
什么也没找到
I've got nothing.
他来了
There he is.
很高兴见到你  长官
Happy to see you, sir.
崔普利特特工  斯凯
Agent Triplett, Skye.
长官
Sir.
让我俩单独谈谈行吗
Can you give us a moment?
好的
Watch this.
不会吧  都不来个拥抱吗
What? No hugs?
他挺期待的呢
He was really looking forward to it.
我交叉对比了实验室记录
I've cross-checked the writing from the lab
和你给我的图片
with the new images you've given me.
大多一致
Mostly the same,
但是解码员还没有找到什么
but the code breakers haven't found anything --
我不是为那事来的
That's not why I'm here.
任务中你们遇到的那个刀枪不入的杀手
The bulletproof assassin you encountered on the sting?
我们查出身份了
We know who he is.
你想让我下去一趟  是吗
You want me to go down there, don't you?
只有你能办到
You're the only one who can.
只有这种事才能
Is this really what it takes for you and I
让我们单独见上一面吗
to get a one-on-one these days?
为什么现在让我去
Why now?
因为现行技术有保障了
Because the technology in play warrants it.
那我有的选择吗
And do I have a say in this?
遵命就是
Copy that.
底下有道惯性约束激光屏障
There's an inertial confinement laser barrier down there,
很厉害
which is cool.
按这个键可以隔音
Now this button turns it soundproof.
按这个让它透明
This button makes it opaque.
地下室D
只要告诉我
Just tell me there isn't
没有不小心会碰到的"关闭"键就行
an "Off" button I can accidentally hit.
你很安全  我保证
You'll be safe. I promise.
地下室D
见到你真是让人赏心悦目
Aren't you a sight for sore eyes.
我几周前就跟科尔森说
I told Coulson weeks ago
我想跟你谈
that I was willing to speak to you --
提供点情报
to give you intelligence.
为什么现在
Why now?
有什么坏事发生吗
Something bad happen?
卡尔·克里尔
Carl Creel.
加勒特上报说他死了  结果他还活着
Garrett reported him dead. Turns out he's alive.
这件事你知情吗
Do you have any information on that?
你最近怎么样
How have you been?
这个名字听着耳熟
The name sounds familiar.
有照片吗
Do you have a picture?
科尔森没告诉你
Coulson didn't tell you.
我经历了一段艰难的日子
I went through a... rough stretch.
他们给我的第一条裤子
First pair of pants they gave me had a --
背面有一颗扣子
a button on the back.
他们把扣子拿走了
They took that away.
如果你巧妙地折叠一张纸
But you fold a piece of paper just right,
它就会变得锋利
it gets sharp.
当他们把那纸也拿走时  我开始撞墙
When they took that away, I started running at the walls.
你该撞得更狠点
You should have run faster.
这一切都过去了
I'm through all that.
当我从镇静剂中醒来  我的脑袋非常清醒
When I came out of sedation, I was clear-headed,
我开始接受
Accepting...
自己的身份  所做过的事
of who I am, what I've done,
以及原因
and why.
这样做真的好吗
You sure about this?
让沃德如愿以偿
Giving Ward exactly what he wants?
他当然会说他只和斯凯谈
Of course he said he'd only talk to Skye.
他想用谎言来说服她
He wants to fill her head with lies.
目前为止他说的都不是谎话
He hasn't lied yet.
你的手臂就不同了
Your arms tell a different story.
看得出梅一直在训练你
I see May's training you.
她先让你习惯了用左手
She's got you favoring your left side first
因为你是右撇子  聪明
'cause you're right-handed. Smart.
我只说一次
I'm gonna say this once.
我不会相信你说的任何一句话
I'm not gonna believe a word that comes out of your mouth.
但只要你的回答
But if a single word is about
与我问的问题无关
anything other than the question that I'm asking,
我立刻走人
I walk.
好
Okay.
克里尔曾是个拳击手  绰号粉碎者
Creel was a boxer, nicknamed the Crusher.
当你手套下有一副铁拳时
Turns out any opponent has a glass jaw
任何对手都不堪一击
when you have steel fists under your gloves.
加勒特认为他有利用价值
Garrett thought he'd be an asset.
一旦克里尔接触了一种物质
Now, once Creel touches a substance,
他就能将其吸收  并且能有意识地
he can absorb it and somehow consciously transform
把身体的分子转化成那种物质
the molecules of his body into that substance.
他不愿告诉我们是怎么做到的
He wouldn't tell us how,
但他很享受那种感觉
But he enjoys the way it feels...
几乎跟他享受杀戮的感觉一样
Almost as much as he enjoys killing.
那你们俩一定很投机
You two must have gotten along great.
这挺有趣  但是毫无意义
Well, this was fun but pointless.
我们已经弄明白了这点
We've already figured that stuff out,
-所以如果你不知道他的藏身之处  -等等
- so if you don't know where to find him, then -- - wait.
当九头蛇与神盾局内部人员通信的时候
When Hydra was communicating with S.H.I.E.L.D.,
我们会在神盾局的
we'd use white noise in the gaps
量子密匙分配频道之间的空隙使用白噪音
between S.H.I.E.L.D.'s quantum key distribution channels
来隐藏信息
to hide messages.
现在神盾局或许消失了
Now, S.H.I.E.L.D. might be gone,
但那些频率还在
but not those frequencies.
如果九头蛇在给克里尔下达指令
If Hydra is giving commands to Creel,
他们一定会这么做
that'll be how.
我们很快就能知道了
We'll see.
这是真的  包括我的余生
It's true, and so will be every word I say to you
对你所说的每一句话
for the rest of my life.
我不是在求你原谅
I'm not asking for forgiveness.
我只想帮你
I just want to help you.
等证实这些资料的真实性后
And when that information proves true,
我希望你会回来
I hope you'll come back.
有很多事我想告诉你
There's so much I want to tell you about...
是关于你父亲的
your father.
收到新指令
信不信由你们
And believe it or not,
有人正通过那些频道下达了一条指令
there's a directive going out over those channels right now.
我可以发送回应请求
Now, I can ping an echo request,
看看是否有其他人接收
see if there's other receivers out there,
看看有多少九头蛇特工能用这方法通信
how many Hydra agents can communicate this way.
这么说他没说谎
So he's telling the truth.
看来是的
It looks like it.
谢谢
Thank you.
看来这次探视只是个开头  是吧
I guess that visit was the first of many, huh?
我们把沃德扣留在这是有原因的
We kept Ward here for this reason,
现在也得到了回报
and it's paying off.
他想要什么
What is his deal?
我真的不知道
I really don't know,
但这并不重要
But it doesn't matter,
只要他让我们能洞悉
As long as he's giving us an inside look
九头蛇的行动
at Hydra's operations.
伙计们  关于这事
Yeah, guys? About that.
你说对了
You called it.
塔伯特没能瓦解九头蛇
Talbot hasn't crushed hydra.
只是让他们回到了地下活动
Just sent them slithering back to the shadows.
真不想说对
I hate being right.
海军
The navy?
他说的吗  你开玩笑吧
He said that? You must be kidding me.
波多马克广场  华盛顿
他说他喜欢船
He said he likes boats.
他只是喜欢和他老爸乱开玩笑而已
He likes messing with his old man is what it is.
别跑太远
Don't go far.
抱歉
Excuse me.
-海军吗  -没错
- The navy. - Yep.
我得告诉你  这事我一定会有意见的
I'll tell you what -- I'll have something to say about that.
亲爱的  他才11岁而已
Sweetheart, he's 11.
我相信你很快就会让他丧失兴趣的
I'm sure you'll wear him down soon enough.
-格伦  -怎么了
- Glenn. -Yeah?
你电话在响
Your phone's ringing.
不是我的...
That's not my --
带上乔治
Take George.
-马上回到车里  -什么
- Get to the car now. - What?
-现在就去  -知道了
- Now! - Okay. All right.
你是谁
Who is this?
塔伯特准将  你有危险
General Talbot, you're in danger.
我们是来保护你的  请听仔细了
We're here to ensure your safety. Please listen carefully.
科尔森特工  是你吗
Agent Coulson, is this you?
出来吧  我们才好说话啊
Show yourself so we can talk about it.
没时间了  我们是来保护你的
There's no time. We're here to protect you.
听我说
Listen to me.
不  你听我说
No, you listen to me.
我有自己的安保人员
I have my own protection
还在关塔那摩准备了间牢房等你
and a cell for you at Gitmo.
我是塔伯特
This is Talbot.
我现在需要增援
I need reinforcements at my location now.
小心身后
Watch your six!
行动  行动
Move, move, move!
抓住那个混蛋
Secure that bastard!
行动  行动
Move, move! Go, go!
准将  快转移到安全地点吧
General, let's get you to a covered spot.
行动  行动
Go, go!
准将  我们得把你转移到安全地点
General, we should get you somewhere safe.
准将
General?
又见面了
Hi, again.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
真有必要把我绑起来吗
Are these straps really necessary?
你说呢
You tell me.
我猜有必要  为了确保你的安全
I guess. To ensure your safety.
我希望我们能合作
I'm hoping we can work together,
重拾昔日友情
be buddies like we used to be.
友情
"Buddies"?
我们上次见面的时候
Last time we saw each other,
你攻击了我和我的部队
you assaulted me and my team.
为了阻止一个杀手  我也做到了
So I could go stop a killer, which I did.
而你找到了那个秘密基地
Whereas you discovered that secret base.
还得到了晋升  空军准将塔伯特
Got a big promotion, Brigadier General Talbot.
这么看来我们关系还真不错呢
Sounds like a pair of best buds to me.
我得说
I got to say...
我很佩服你
I respect you.
你成功躲避了我们整个冬天
You managed to evade us for an entire winter.
我也佩服你  能让我这么费劲
And I respect you for making it so damn hard.
简直让我精疲力尽
I'm exhausted.
我猜也是
I'll bet.
现在我想让你轻松点
But I want to make your job easier.
追捕我们就是浪费资源  准将
Chasing us is a waste of resources, general.
我们都是好人
We're the good guys,
我们能帮你们抓住坏人
and we can help you catch the bad guys.
绑架我  把我关在你的蜂窝杀人房里
Kidnapping me and tying me up in your honeycomb kill room
可不怎么有说服力
is not helping your case.
你觉得我是白痴吗
Do you think I'm an idiot?
不  你很明白
Oh, no. You're the real deal.
但你周围的人
But you're surrounded by people
都低估了他们所面临的威胁
who constantly underestimate the threat they're up against.
我和我的团队都会坚守自己的誓言
Me and my people swore an oath we don't intend to break --
保护无辜者  照顾大家
To protect the innocent, to watch out for people --
那些像你儿子这样的人
People like your son.
你别想把我家人牵扯进来
How dare you bring my family into this.
我们拯救生命
We save lives,
包括你的在内  不管你愿意与否
including yours, whether you like it or not.
进展得真顺利
That was smooth.
激怒他  让他紧抓扶手
Riled him up, got him to grab the arm rests.
已完成89%
现在有效指纹分析  完成89%
And now active fingerprint analysis -- 89%.
我们是为了保护你们
We were there for your protection.
确保大家安全  没人受伤
Everyone safe, no one got hurt.
看看凯尼格  在那做分析
Look at Koenig, running analysis.
我们好像有个新金童了
Well, it looks like we've got our new golden boy.
新金童  以前有旧的吗
"New"? As opposed to the original?
没错  我啊
Yes. Me.
我现在只能靠边站了
And I've been sidelined.
不是的
No.
我是说  或许是有一点
Well, I mean, maybe,
但那就像在足球比赛中
but in the way that a player is sidelined
受伤的球员只好在旁观战
due to injury in a football match.
足球还是美式足球
Football or American football?
因为现在开脑袋创伤笑话  西蒙斯
'Cause a head-trauma joke right now, Simmons,
真的是很低级趣味  对你来说都是
that's in severely poor taste, even for you.
我看到他们是怎么看我的
And I see the way they look at me.
尤其当他们一直问我
Especially when they keep on asking about the...
-隐形装置  -是的
- Cloaking. - Yeah.
不  他们只是有点担心
No, they're just anxious about it.
他们知道你快完工了
They know you're nearly done.
是啊  我可能没以前那么天才了
Yeah, well, I may not seem like the genius I used to be,
但我还是有想法的
but I still have ideas.
-是的  -我就是现在有困难
- Yeah. - I'm just having a hard time...
我只是难于...
I'm just having...
-表达  -对
- Expressing them. - Yeah.
这  这并不意味着
And that -- that doesn't mean
他们就得那么对我
that they have to treat me like...
怎么对你  菲兹
Like what, Fitz?
就像我随时会崩溃一般
Treat me like I'm gonna break.
这很让我烦心
It's distracting.
而跟你说话是唯一让我觉得思路清晰的时候
And, you know, talking to you is the only time I feel clear.
也很平静
And calm.
就像我真的可能好起来似的
Like I might actually get better.
你已经在好转了  每天都是
You are getting better. Every day.
我能看到  他们能看到
I see it, they see it,
很快你自己也能看到
and soon you'll see it yourself.
是吧
Yeah.
他们真的应该分析言语模式
You know, they really should be analyzing speech patterns
追踪语音
and tracking voice...
-语音生物特征  -生物特征
- Voice biometrics. - biometrics.
是的  菲兹  我想他们在做了
Yes, Fitz, I think they are.
科尔森  我觉得我们在这事上看法不同
Coulson, I don't think we see eye-to-eye on this.
我的队伍完全有能力
My team was up to the task
抓住那个变态
when they took that freak into custody,
在你抓走我之前
before you took me.
他们已经将他关了起来
They have him on lockdown.
-这就是问题所在  -这有什么问题
- That's the problem. - How is that a problem?
你在无数公开露面中都说过
You've said in your numerous public appearances
你有一个基地专门用来存放神盾突击队
that you have a facility where you're storing the technology
缴获的技术和囚犯  对吗
and prisoners captured in the S.H.I.E.L.D. raids, yes?
是  我很荣幸你一直关注我的新闻
Yeah.I'm flattered you keep up with my press.
你的重点是什么
What's your point?
克里尔在找那个基地里的一件致命武器
Creel's after a deadly weapon stored in that facility.
这些还有些新闻
Here's some more press.
他原本想以你的家人迫使你交出
He targeted your family to force you to give up
新指令
信息提取议题
陆军准将格伦·塔伯特
那个基地的地点  但现在他不用了
the location of that facility, but now he doesn't have to.
你的人刚刚抓了一个他们无法控制的人
Your people just took a man they have no idea how to contain
送到了他正想去的地方
to the one place he wants to be.
现在我需要你帮忙阻止他
Now I need your help to stop him.
我跟你做个交易
I'll make you a deal.
你放我出去  我保证不会杀你
You let me out of here, and I promise not to kill you.
但我对天发誓
But there is no way on God's green earth
我绝不可能帮你
I am ever gonna help you.
你会的
You might.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
我是陆军准将格伦·塔伯特
This is Brigadier General Glenn Talbot,
访问码D365SVN
access code delta-3-6-5-sierra-victor-niner.
用双倍人手押送那个囚犯
I want double detail on that prisoner.
围墙上布满半自动步枪手
I want the walls crawling with semi-autos,
还有马上派车来我现在的位置
and a vehicle at my location now!
是  长官
Uh, absolutely, sir.
我们  我们马上安排
We'll -- we'll get right on that.
VN  N
Victor-niner. Niner.
好了  对
Okay. Yeah, all right.
您  您等一下  将军
You just -- you hold tight, General.
好的  我们通过追踪号码
Okay, we, uh, traced the number to
找到五角大楼附近的一处地点
a spot near the Pentagon.
随时可以出发
We are ready to go.
我们有个小小的逻辑问题
We have a small logic question.
为什么  为什么我们要进去
Why? Why are we going in?
-我们相信科尔森的判断  -有吗
- Look, we trust Coulson's judgment. - We do?
但塔伯特人不坏
But Talbot's not a bad guy.
而且据我所知
And last I checked,
美国政府并不算是最邪恶的
the U.S. government is one of the lesser evils.
现在武器被他们锁在箱子里
So they've got the weapon in a locked box.
而这个"吸收人"也将被他们
And now they've got this absorbing man
关进箱子里
in a locked box, too.
-这不是坏事吧  -她说得没错
- That's not so bad. - She's got a point.
那里看起来像是一个安全收押他们的地方
It does seem as safe a place to keep them as any.
他们不知道自己面对的是什么状况
They have no idea what they're dealing with.
对  但这风险难道还能大过
Yeah, but is that danger worse than the risk
指派如今所有的全部神盾局特工
of sending every field operative you have available
去一个安全军事基地吗
into a secure military compound?
是啊  还是由那群追捕我们的人守卫
Yeah, guarded by the same people that's been hunting us.
深入虎穴啊  哥们
Belly of the beast, man.
我们已经自身难保了
Well, we're already on our heels.
如今连这架飞机都不能用
We can't even get this thing out of the hangar.
确实
Exactly.
现在是决定性的时刻
This is a make-or-break moment.
为了一个我们一无所知的东西
For an object we have zero data on.
那不是我们唯一要得到的东西
That's not the only thing we're after.
要么全盘接受要么彻底放弃
Now it's all or nothing, huh?
那好吧
Well, all right, then.
你负责这次行动吗
You taking point?
科尔森通过无线通信指挥
Coulson will be on comms.
这次任务我们一定要互相照应
Hey, let's stick together on this one.
没问题
You got it.
准将
General.
别这样  你知道我看起来帅呆了
Come on, girl. You know I look good.
不  他们说准将塔伯特就这么消失了
No, they're saying general Talbot up and vanished.
不知是怎么做到的
Don't know how.
可能这人耍了什么魔术吧
Think this guy might have pulled some kind of magic trick.
怎么回事
What the...
人不见了  通知楼上
He's gone. Call upstairs.
我来送琼斯将军和他的同事
I have General Jones and his party here
与塔伯特准将见面
to meet with General Talbot.
琼斯将军
General Jones?
先生  抱歉
Sir. I'm sorry, sir.
今天的预约记录中没有您的名字
I don't have this visit in the register today.
你最好再仔细查查
You might want to double-check that.
军事基地的所有线路都被隐藏了
Military installations bury all their cables.
非常聪明
Wisely.
也没有什么了不起
Not that wisely.
输入访问密码
D365SV
Okay. Delta-3-6-5-sierra-victor--
N
Niner.
如果没有登记  我也帮不了您
If it's not in here, there's nothing I can do.
出口左转  谢谢
Exit to the left, please.
-门岗  -我是塔伯特准将
- Gatehouse. - This is General Talbot.
士兵  为什么琼斯将军和他的护卫
Why has General Jones and his government escort
在门口受到了阻拦
been delayed at the gate, soldier?
放他们过去
Wave them through.
抱歉  长官
Uh, sir. Sorry, sir.
他的名字没有登记  我得严格按照指令
His name's not in the register, and my orders are to strictly --
-听好了  小子  -二等兵蒂尔登
- you listen to me, son. - Private Tilden.
-是二等兵蒂尔登吗  -是的  长官
- It's Private Tilden, isn't it? - Yes, sir.
我不管什么登记册
Well, I don't care about this register or that.
我需要琼斯将军和他的人
I want General Jones and his friends sent
直接到军械库来见我
directly to the ordnance depot to meet me.
再狠一点
Go bigger. Go bigger.
否则我会把你扔进粪坑
...Or I'll have you so deep in horse manure, son,
你他妈得准备个气管
you'll need a damn snorkel.
我明白  长官  但我不能
I understand, sir, but I can't --
琼斯将军
没问题了  长官
Oh. Never mind sir.
算你识相  大兵
Nice work, Soldier.
下次见我的时候可以来和我握手
Next time you see me, come shake my hand.
挂了
Talbot out.
允许进入  格伦·塔伯特
待在这别熄火  以免我们中止行动
Stay and keep it running in case we have to abort.
明白
Got it.
简直是大海捞针
Needle in a haystack.
看来我一点都没夸大
Turns out I was not exaggerating.
好了  我们都知道要找什么
All right, we know what we're looking for.
是吧
Don't we?
战略科学军团物资  139号
我找到了084
I've got the 0-8-4.
重复  我找到这个破玩意了
Repeat -- I've got the damn thing.
西南方向
Southwest side.
好吧  让我们来看看为什么这东西是致命武器
Okay. Why don't we find out what makes this thing so deadly?
不
Aah! No!
怎么回事
What the hell's happening?
我没法松开
I can't let go!
哈特利  手放松
Okay,  Hartley,  just relax your hand.
我松不开
I can't let go.
别碰它
Don't touch it.
离远点
Just stay away.
他们马上就追过来了
They'll be on us any second.
该撤了  帮我扶她起来  你能走吗
Okay, time to go. Help me get her up. Can you walk?
应该吧
I think so.
还在等什么
What are you waiting for?!
再不把她弄出去我们都得死
We need to get her out of here before we all get killed!
我们已经达到来这儿的目的了
We got what we came for!
还有其他的东西
Not everything we came for.
等等  你说什么
Wait. What are you talking about?
科尔森  哈特利找到那个东西了
Coulson, Hartley has the item,
但现在那东西在侵蚀她
but it's attacking her.
她现在急需救治  中止任务吗
She needs medical right now. Do we abort?
警报已触发
Alarms have sounded.
他们很有可能被抓或被杀
Chances of them being captured or killed here just skyrocketed.
我们要终止行动吗
Should we just cut our losses?
科尔森
Coulson?!
快点  快点
Come on! Come on!
长官  重复一遍  我们的命令是什么
S-sir, I repeat -- what are our orders?
我们要撤退吗
Do we go dark?
不
Negative.
不要撤退  按计划继续行动
Do not abort. Proceed as planned.
你们都听到了
You heard him.
扶我站起来  我能跟上
Help me up. I can follow.
-你疯了吗  -我们必须服从命令
- Are you mental? - We have our orders.
让命令见鬼去吧  我们得帮你找个医生
Screw the orders. We need to get you to a doctor.
亨特
Hunter --
不不  你们想留在这里送死随你们的便
No, no, stay here and die if that's what you want to do,
但我不会让她死的
but I'm making sure she doesn't.
我真心祝你们好运  但我们先走了
I wish you the best of luck, really, but we're out of here.
上  上
Go! Go!
-他们往西门跑了  -上  快上
- They're headed to the west door! - Move! Move! Go! Go!
快把我们弄出去
Get us the hell out of here!
没问题
You got it.
把它砍掉
Cut it off.
什么  不
What? N-no.
我们马上送你去医院  他们会治好你的
We'll get you to a hospital. They'll fix this.
这东西在杀死我  我能感觉到
This thing is killing me. I can feel it.
我需要你把它砍掉
I need you to cut it off,
否则我撑不到医院
or I won't make it to the hospital.
没什么大不了的
It's no big deal.
你也知道现在的假肢技术有多先进
You've seen what they can do with robotics these days.
或许比真的还好使呢
Uh, probably be an upgrade.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
好吧
Okay.
我知道风险很大
I know it was a risk.
如果我们今天失败了
If we went down today,
可能就彻底失败了
we'd probably be down for good.
但现在我们有了一线生机
But now we have a chance to survive.
我们有不畏牺牲的士兵
We have soldiers willing to sacrifice,
但他们需要武器
but they need weapons.
敌人有他们的优势
The enemy has the advantage.
我们需要自己的优势
We need one of our own.
你冒险就是为了一架昆式战斗机吗
You risked that for a quinjet?
不  是为了它能让我们做到的事
No. For what we can do with one.
消失
Disappear.
变成鬼魂
Become ghosts.
我们现在必须这样生存
That's how we have to live now --
站在阴影中保护人们
in the shadows, to save people,
即使他们不知道也不想要我们的保护
even when they don't know it, don't want it.
菲兹说他能做出隐形装置  但是
Fitz said he could engineer cloaking, but...
我担心他什么都做不出
I'm afraid he can't do anything.
他的大脑颞叶大面积受损
The damage to his temporal lobe was too extensive.
他已经不是以前的他了  而
He's not the same, and...
自从西蒙斯走后  他的情况更加恶化了
since Simmons left, he's only getting worse.
这是五个里面的第二个
And this is number two of five.
不过如果我们今天能搞定这个
But if we get this one finished today,
剩下的就不多了  西蒙斯
there's not much -- Simmons,
我说了不要乱碰
I said not to touch anything.
你可能会
You'll get --
是的  是的  我知道  我知道
Yes, yes. I know. I know.
我已经听你的话  告诉他们耐心一点了
And I have told them to be patient, like you said,
但我还是没法连接那个
but I'm still having trouble communicating the...
那个  是的
the -- yes.
谢谢
Thank you.
对不起
Sorry.
西蒙斯说
Simmons said
她觉得如果她不在他的情况会好些
she thought he'd be better without her here,
但是她的离开让他彻底垮掉了
but her leaving just broke him.
几个月来  他越来越孤僻
In the months since, he's grown isolated,
总是自言自语
talking to himself more and more.
我知道
I know.
我知道  我快成功了
I know. I'm almost there.
我们必须为了他
We have to fight on for him,
为了我们失去的人们坚持战斗
for those we've lost.
我们必须冒险
We have to take risks,
才不会让他们的牺牲白白浪费
so the sacrifices they made were not made in vain.
所以接下来
And then...
我们消失
we'll disappear.
克里尔已经逃出来并拿到了方尖碑
Creel has escaped and did indeed make off with the Obelisk.
他应该很快就会联系我们
He should contact us shortly.
我本想直接让他来这里
I would have him come in,
不过我对这次行动非常谨慎
but I'm being overly discreet with this operation.
我知道你找这个
I know how long
已经很久了  怀特霍尔博士
you have been searching for this, Dr. Whitehall.
你根本想象不到有多久
You have no idea.